Now ready, the bath.
Don't sink with it.
Where are your parents?
At work.
But with this snow, they might be back soon.
Wouldn't that be bad?
Why would that be bad?
How did things turn out like this?
Sorry, you should do it yourself!
Never asked you to do it in the first place.
The bath is now ready.
Feel free to use our shampoo and stuff.
Okay.
Chill out, man.
Don't be a creep.
Just be cool.
No, hang on!
I'm about to be buck naked in Yamada's house!
Why did I waltz in like it's no big deal?
Is it warm enough?
Uh, I'm not even in yet.
Uh, it smells like Yamada in here.
Okay, shampoo.
Stop!
Quit looking for traces of her!
This is too much.
I can't stay in here long.
Ichikawa!
Hey!
What is it?
I left a change of clothes here.
Also, I'll put your uniform in a bag.
Uh, don't worry about me.
Now I've gone and talked to her with my hands on the goods!
Yes!
Thank you.
Come on, think this over, man!
She feels responsible for your arm
and the whole keychain incident.
Jeez.
Think about how she must feel.
Huh?
Why this?
Don't people usually just borrow clothes
from the men in the house at times like this?
Huh? Oh, no.
Wait. Hang on.
Hang on.
My underwear.
They're gone.
Are they in her bag with the rest of my clothes?
I guess I could just slip this on,
grab my underwear,
and head straight to the bathroom.
Wait.
Just go full commando, though?
And this?
Guess I'll wash it before I give it back anyway.
And it's only for a second.
I forgot about this little guy!
Oh, you're out?
Hey!
Tell me, which one do you prefer,
chonko or chicken?
She's in underwear!
What are you talking about?
This wouldn't be silly.
Hot Pod.
We have a whole set ready,
so I'm just gonna toss it in.
Since when was it decided we were doing lunch?
Oh, then I guess...
Don't let your mines go there!
Let it go!
Empty the mines.
You are cast in a sea of death.
If you slip up, it's all over.
I need my underwear!
Where?
No!
I'm done for!
This is it!
Stay!
Lay down!
Okay.
Oh, sorry!
It's fine.
Everything's in place.
That was close.
Why'd you change?
This was a gift from Moeko.
Thought it might be a lot cuter to wear, so...
Huh?
Why don't you sit down?
I thought it might be a lot cuter to wear, so...
Huh?
Why don't you sit down?
Right next to me.
So, um, whenever my mom's late, I have hot pot before dinner. By myself.
Before dinner?
Pretty awesome, right? Solo hot pot.
All grown up and mature.
More like lonely and a bit depressing, actually.
Then... will you... come over and eat with me sometime?
Hey, didn't you bring something with you?
Oh, yeah! Feaked your interest, huh?
Not really.
Hmph. Too bad. We're looking at it.
Oh, your yearbook.
Wow. I didn't think I'd get to peek at a old yearbook this soon.
There.
Oh, it's so you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Already in her final form.
Is this from a class trip?
Yeah. We went to Nikko.
You're eating in every shot.
Oh, there you are.
You're even faster than I am.
Huh?
Do you play piano?
I took lessons for a bit when I was a kid.
Oh.
For about a year.
Hmm.
Then there was ballet, and language, then swimming and kendo.
I quit all of them pretty quick, though.
You did that much?
I guess.
Hmm.
I got to do all sorts of stuff like that.
But no matter what I did, I wasn't as good as everyone else was.
I hated how new kids would get so much better than me.
My folks picked up on it fast, though, and let me quit right away.
In fact, we had a whole tradition where they'd make my favorite food on the days I quit something.
When I failed my exams, and when I hurt my nose.
Your folks sound nice.
Yep.
Although, I'm a bit worried.
Huh?
I'm surrounded by so many great people.
That's why I never realize when I'm being such a burden on them.
At this rate, one day, I'm going to burden them too much, and then it's going to make them hate me.
Yamada.
Ah, sorry.
Look at me all teary-eyed.
I don't know how your parents feel, but I think people would tell you when you're too much or when they've had enough.
They'd be straight with you.
I've said as much before.
Hey, can I ask you something that's been on my mind for a bit?
Huh?
Back before winter break, there were two days you didn't come hang out in the library, remember?
You said you had stuff to do, but did you really?
I've been wondering.
You said you could be straight and let me know when things are just too much for you.
But I don't think you can.
I mean, I know.
I know you're way too nice to say something.
It scares me.
I'm so sorry about this.
I know I must be such a pain.
Wait.
I'm sorry I lied.
I just didn't have it in me.
I didn't want to get hurt.
So, of course, I closed myself off.
I was just afraid she'd hate me.
That's right.
We're a bit alike.
Napa cabbage is best when mushy.
Don't fill it to the brim like that.
Here.
It's funny.
I've been this exact way my whole life.
So why am I suddenly worried about silly things like this now?
I guess maybe...
It's just because I...
It could be because you've grown up.
Grown-ups can get annoying.
You're right.
Guess that's true as well.
Getting worried is a good thing.
If you ask me,
I think your parents treated you that way when you suddenly quit stuff like that
because they didn't want you to stop trying new things.
They knew you would cheer up and ultimately keep moving on.
Oh, line.
When did I get so many messages?
What's wrong?
My mom was at the convenience store that's just nearby.
Twelve minutes ago.
Don't worry.
I have friends over all the time.
Yeah, but not guy friends.
Well, no.
But even still...
I mean...
Come on.
Look how I'm dressed.
If I'm to meet her, I want to be dressed right.
Oh, you're right.
Then maybe...
You can come back in proper clothes?
At some point...
Hurry!
Oh, hey!
Welcome home!
Do you have a friend over?
Yeah.
She's here.
Yeah?
Oh.
You got the bath ready for me.
That was nice of you.
Okay.
Once she gets in the bath, I'll make a run for it.
So this is Yamada's room.
That's her bed.
Come on!
Now's not the time to think like that!
I just forced her into a lie.
If she gets caught, I'll be the one to blame for ruining their relationship.
Oh, had yourself some hot pot.
Ah!
Yep.
Anna's specialty.
All right.
And you're dressed up so cute this afternoon, too.
Mm-hmm.
Moeko gave this to me as a present.
I was cold, so I thought I'd put it on to get warm.
I've got something just like that.
Maybe I'll wear mine, too.
That's a great idea.
So hurry and go get warmed up.
No, wait!
My dad is going to be home soon!
What?!
Your dad?!
What's he like?
I mean...
He's a bit...
like, um...
Is he...
like you?
No, he's...
He's delicious!
Poster here!
Anna!
Oh, hey!
What's the matter, Mom?
Is that hot pot okay with Qi?
Does she have any allergies?
Uh, she's fine.
Anna ate most of it anyway.
Um, thanks for having me over.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I sure hope so.
But the snow's still coming down.
So don't stay too late.
Sorry.
No, I'm the one who should be saying that.
Hm?
For making you lie.
Sorry.
Uh...
Mm-hmm.
Hm?
Ah!
Oof!
Ah...
That's fine.
I mean, sure, I had never lied to my mom before this, but I am grown up now. So there.
A grown-up who refers to herself by name at home?
That's secret!
See ya!
Talk about a day full of secrets!
It's a giant!
These high-rise apartments are terrifying!
I'm never coming back!
Huh?
Had no choice but to hand wash.
Couldn't get caught using the washing machine.
Wait, if I use different detergent than she uses at home, that could cause all sorts of trouble.
Maybe I should wait and ask her first.
Huh?
When did you get in here?
God, you're such a pervert!
Is it really all that different?
Laundry always smells different at people's houses.
Hmm?
Smells like nothing.
Sure was plenty of trouble just washing and giving this back.
What a mess.
You've got this, KyoTaro!
Got what?
Shamana, duh.
Think about what happened between you two.
A bath?
Hot pot?
A hug?
It's all proof of only one thing, my man.
No, you're wrong about that.
Actually, she was going to introduce me to her parents if I didn't stop her from doing it.
Because I'm nothing special, just a normal friend.
You call that being a friend?
In what way?
I mean, I don't really know what having friends is like.
Me either.
Finally free from my cast.
But something's up with my voice.
Oh!
Hey, your cast is off now.
I noticed this cast was off first.
Get this.
Yesterday, Yamada ate six whole rice balls all by herself.
I only ate five, but six the day before.
That's the correction you want to make?
I'm glad you enjoyed them.
That's good old Ichikawa for you.
Always cheerleading.
Yep.
Wouldn't be him if he wasn't that way.
Hey, is your arm all right?
Still can't lift heavy stuff.
Look, my right arm got all skinny.
Ichikawa?
Huh?
Something's wrong.
Hmm.
It's not that I don't want to talk.
Hey, where's Adachi?
He chose to take dancing instead.
I'm no good when it comes to dancing.
I'm glad you're in this class with me.
Yeah, same here.
Uh-
I think perhaps my uniform might smell.
Yeah, I've heard the school ones always smell a bit.
Does it smell that bad?
It does.
Oh, God.
I'd give her mine, but that might seem a little weird.
We're going to practice sparring today.
Everyone pair up.
All alone.
Let's partner up.
All right.
No problem.
I'll be easy.
I'll just go over here.
Is she?
Could it be?
Pay attention.
The Ochigari throw is like this.
Nice fall there.
All right, begin.
Oh, man.
I bet Hara is so strong.
Okay, like this?
Good.
That's the way.
Oh, yeah.
Bring it on.
Is this really us being friends?
Sorry.
Right now, I really stink a bit.
I mean, my uniform really stinks.
That's right.
You don't want to spar with anyone else, right?
Uh.
That's payback.
You and Yama sure get along well, don't you?
No.
She just, well, truthfully, she smells now.
Uh.
Smelly girls are the best.
No, that's not.
Uh.
My voice must be changing.
I talked big about growing up, but I'm the one who's afraid of it.
Once I'm an adult, there's no way she and I can keep our relationship the same.
Especially if she only thinks of me the same as all her girlfriends.
Trustworthy and safe.
I'm not sure there's any way around this, but straight through.
It's just hard to speak.
If I talk louder, my voice just starts to crack.
Do you have a cold then?
No.
Um.
You were out in the snow for a while and all.
It's not that.
This isn't a cold.
I think my voice is just changing now.
Hmm?
Is that it?
That's so cool.
Wow.
Oh my gosh.
How is this cool?
You guys get brand new voices and even some facial hair.
It's so easy for people to tell when you finally grow up.
That's the part I hate.
Time for some red bean rice.
That's not how that goes.
Oh, your arm.
Hmm?
Your arms.
Maybe this one didn't get skinny, but this one just got a lot bigger instead.
Huh?
You know?
A sign of growing older I never noticed.
So exciting.
Yamada's always the one who helps me realize.
Itchikawa, once your voice finally gets deeper,
make sure you say my name plenty.
I, um...
Huh?
Yamada's growing up too!
You've got this.
Go get it.
Do it, Kyo Taro.